https://utilitygeek.com/privacy-policy/

ReviewsHow ToNewsWeb PrivacyWhat Is a VPN Connection?
Search
Friday, December 11, 2020
Utility Geek ReviewsHow ToNewsWeb PrivacyWhat Is a VPN Connection?Home
Privacy Policy Privacy PolicyYour privacy is important to us. It is Utility Geek’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://utilitygeek.com, and other sites we own and operate.We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.Popular ArticlesHow to Use a VPN on Mac and Why It’s Important December 31, 20182609 Getting a VPN is important in this day and age. But many people don’t know how to set up a VPN on Mac, and...What Are the Alternatives to the Pirate Bay? January 24, 2019The Best VPN for Online Gaming December 7, 2018Choosing the Best VPN for Windows 10: All You Need to... January 31, 2019How and Why Use a VPN on Xbox One January 10, 2019How and Why You Should Use NordVPN with Reddit January 24, 2019Privacy PolicyAbout UsContact Us © Utility Geek 2019. All rights reserved.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkNoPrivacy policyRevoke cookies
